<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Chatter</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Chatter</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:39:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GP</title>
      <link>/p/gp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:39:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/gp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 best translators you can use in 2023</title>
      <link>/p/the-5-best-translators-you-can-use-in-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:39:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/the-5-best-translators-you-can-use-in-2023/</guid>
      <description>The 5 best translators you can use in 2023 by 4RC4N3 W4s T4K3N</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homework Archive</title>
      <link>/p/homework-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:09:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/homework-archive/</guid>
      <description>Just a collection of my various projects and assignments.
English Summers are getting hotter every year, right? I remember playing outside with my friends for hours without feeling too hot. But now, it&amp;rsquo;s really hard to be outside without feeling like we&amp;rsquo;re melting! Even at night, I have to use the air conditioning to sleep comfortably.
Over the years, temperature changes have been pretty noticeable, especially now with global warming and all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report</title>
      <link>/p/report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 21:36:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/report/</guid>
      <description>Global Perspectives THE BED CRISIS And possible solutions. Introduction Hospitals around the world were unable to handle the demand brought on by Covid-19 (also known as the Coronavirus), which resulted in what many refer to as the &amp;ldquo;Bed Crisis,&amp;rdquo; when patients&amp;rsquo; need for beds skyrocketed.
What happened to cause this? During the first few years of the pandemic, little was known about Covid, leaving hospitals and clinics unable to prepare for the onslaught of patients catching Coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dog</title>
      <link>/p/dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 12:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/dog/</guid>
      <description>This is for an English assignment, and is extremely incomplete It was Tuesday and I had a long sports class at school. I was very tired. On the bus ride home, I was excited to see my dog Chewie. He always greeted me at the door with excitement, showing me his toys and asking for treats. Usually, we played for about ten minutes. But when I got home and opened the door, Chewie wasn&amp;rsquo;t there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Should Children Bring Phones to School</title>
      <link>/p/should-children-bring-phones-to-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 14:32:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/should-children-bring-phones-to-school/</guid>
      <description>Children all across the world yearn to bring their phones to school, for educational reasons, and to play music on the bus. Should children be allowed to bring phones to school?
The downsides Phones would give leeway to a lot of academic dishonor, from cheating on exams to using a calculator in maths class. Having a phone in class would make cheating a lot easier.
It would also lead to a lot of liability for the school, as storing a complex electronic device could lead to possible damage to the device, as well as to technological vulnerabilities in the school&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem, making it easier to &amp;ldquo;hack&amp;rdquo; into computers and potentially steal future exam papers/tests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Swimming Is Good for You</title>
      <link>/p/why-swimming-is-good-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:25:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/why-swimming-is-good-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered why so many people choose swimming as their go to form of exercise?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Writing Is Good for Children</title>
      <link>/p/why-writing-is-good-for-children/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 18:50:36 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/why-writing-is-good-for-children/</guid>
      <description>Writing is an important part of any child&amp;rsquo;s education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitters Downfall</title>
      <link>/p/twitters-downfall/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 15:49:43 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/twitters-downfall/</guid>
      <description>Twitter is the worlds largest micro-blogging app, rivaled only by Koo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diary of a Wimpy Kid Diper Överlode Book Review</title>
      <link>/p/diary-of-a-wimpy-kid-diper-%C3%B6verlode-book-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 19:50:28 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/diary-of-a-wimpy-kid-diper-%C3%B6verlode-book-review/</guid>
      <description>Im sure all of you can guess by the title, that there&amp;rsquo;s alot of potty humor in this. I mean, Loded Diper has been an iconic name for as long as I can remember Diper Överlode was an unexpected but welcome addition to the Diary of a Wimpy Kid series, although not containing much, it was an enjoyable read for me and all my classmates.
Spoiler alert! (but you knew that) Educational Value B- Doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain much, but teaches readers the value of music, and how much artists strive for the spotlight, however small that spotlight is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extreme Sports</title>
      <link>/p/extreme-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/extreme-sports/</guid>
      <description>Are Extreme sports dangerous? And do they deserve to be prohibited? What are extreme sports? Extreme sports, also commonly referred to as action sports, are competitive sports that are characterized by high risk. Skateboarding, snowboarding, freestyle skiing, and mountain biking are the sports that are most frequently included in this category.
Extreme sports are typically performed outside the boundaries of traditional mainstream sports and are renowned for their heart-pounding thrills. Motorcycle and snowmobile racing and acrobatic competitions are frequently categorized as &amp;ldquo;extreme,&amp;rdquo; and the term can be interpreted to include risky activities like skydiving and rock climbing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reading</title>
      <link>/reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/reading/</guid>
      <description>My favorite leisure-times Gaming with my friends Writing my blog is this workign </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s It Like Owning a Dog</title>
      <link>/p/whats-it-like-owning-a-dog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 19:44:55 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/whats-it-like-owning-a-dog/</guid>
      <description>Prologue So I&amp;rsquo;m sure you all have debated about having a dog, whether it be as a companion, guard-dog, or a emotional support pet (in my case, yes). But then you realise how much of a pain in the backside it can be, all the way from potty training, to even simple manners&amp;hellip; In that case, this blog is for you.
The upsides We all know how cute dogs are, and even a street dog can smile its way out of a jam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Made This Blog</title>
      <link>/p/why-i-made-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:20:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/p/why-i-made-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding to be able to move readers with your writing. That’s why I decided to create a blog. To Inspire My audience1 Writing a blog allows one to express ones feelings and air out ones judgements about life, It could also affect the readers life by allowing them to:
Improve their quality of life. Increase their day&amp;rsquo;s output. Make something lovely. Lend a hand to others. All of this is possible thanks to the power of a blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I run a blog that is solely dedicated to sharing my daily thoughts and feelings. I use the HUGO platform to build my blog and host it on Netlify. It serves as a personal outlet for me to document and share my innermost thoughts and emotions. My blog doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a specific focus or theme, but it is a place for me to express myself and share my personal experiences with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animations</title>
      <link>/showcase/animations/animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/animations/animations/</guid>
      <description>Fnaf animations! Animations for school projects. Link to GP project (ignore) Canva
Website</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
