<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Inked</title>
        <link>/post/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Inked</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:09:15 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Homework Archive</title>
        <link>/p/homework-archive/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 21:09:15 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/homework-archive/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="/p/homework-archive/hwpain.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Homework Archive" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a collection of my various projects and assignments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;english&#34;&gt;English&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summers are getting hotter every year, right? I remember playing outside with my friends for hours without feeling too hot. But now, it&amp;rsquo;s really hard to be outside without feeling like we&amp;rsquo;re melting! Even at night, I have to use the air conditioning to sleep comfortably.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the years, temperature changes have been pretty noticeable, especially now with global warming and all. I asked my parents about there experiences, and they spoke about how it was much cooler (temperature wise), so much so that they could spend the entire day outside, My grandmother had similar experiences, she talked about how she never really felt hot and used to sleep without the fans on, which makes our modern summers pale in comparison.
the next few summers are predicted to be the warmest ever recorded, and I blame the usual suspects, Global Warming, Climate Change etc. etc.
But I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve heard that before a million times. And yes, you can blame the excessive emissions of greenhouse gases for this ongoing&amp;hellip; trend? The industrial activities that power our smart toilets (and hospitals) release substantial amounts of carbon dioxide (CO2) and other greenhouse gases into the atmosphere. These emissions create a thick layer that traps heat, leading to a gradual increase in global temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;math&#34;&gt;Math&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;html&gt;
&lt;figure class=&#34;video_container&#34;&gt;
  &lt;video controls=&#34;true&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;true&#34; height=&#34;400&#34;&gt;
    &lt;source src=&#34;liviingroom.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/video&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;library&#34;&gt;Library:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;reading-log&#34;&gt;Reading log&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;banished from his home and ends up on an island with his daughter Miranda. Using his magic powers, Prospero creates a powerful storm that brings his enemies to the island. There are also spirits and monsters on the island, which add to the magical atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miranda falls in love with a prince named Ferdinand, and their love blossoms quickly. Throughout the play, Prospero learns the importance of forgiveness and ultimately forgives his brother, reclaiming what is rightfully his. In the end, he gives up his magic powers, emphasizing the theme of personal growth and transformation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;review&#34;&gt;Review&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=4-star.png width=&#34;15%&#34; height=&#34;5%&#34;&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Although the language may be a bit hard to read because it&amp;rsquo;s old-fashioned, &amp;ldquo;The Tempest&amp;rdquo; offers interesting characters, and a touching message about forgiveness and redemption. It is a worthwhile playscript to read&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;global-perspectives&#34;&gt;Global Perspectives&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 56.2500%;
 padding-bottom: 0; box-shadow: 0 2px 8px 0 rgba(63,69,81,0.16); margin-top: 1.6em; margin-bottom: 0.9em; overflow: hidden;
 border-radius: 8px; will-change: transform;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; width: 100%; height: 100%; top: 0; left: 0; border: none; padding: 0;margin: 0;&#34;
    src=&#34;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;www.canva.com&amp;#x2F;design&amp;#x2F;DAFki3IuyVs&amp;#x2F;view?embed&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; allow=&#34;fullscreen&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;www.canva.com&amp;#x2F;design&amp;#x2F;DAFki3IuyVs&amp;#x2F;view?utm_content=DAFki3IuyVs&amp;amp;utm_campaign=designshare&amp;amp;utm_medium=embeds&amp;amp;utm_source=link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Reduce, Reuse, Recycle, Rot, Repair&lt;/a&gt; by Pranav Thandassery
&lt;h2 id=&#34;biology&#34;&gt;Biology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; width: 100%; height: 0; padding-top: 56.2500%;
 padding-bottom: 0; box-shadow: 0 2px 8px 0 rgba(63,69,81,0.16); margin-top: 1.6em; margin-bottom: 0.9em; overflow: hidden;
 border-radius: 8px; will-change: transform;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe loading=&#34;lazy&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; width: 100%; height: 100%; top: 0; left: 0; border: none; padding: 0;margin: 0;&#34;
    src=&#34;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;www.canva.com&amp;#x2F;design&amp;#x2F;DAFkBHmwD60&amp;#x2F;view?embed&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; allow=&#34;fullscreen&#34;&gt;
  &lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;https:&amp;#x2F;&amp;#x2F;www.canva.com&amp;#x2F;design&amp;#x2F;DAFkBHmwD60&amp;#x2F;view?utm_content=DAFkBHmwD60&amp;amp;utm_campaign=designshare&amp;amp;utm_medium=embeds&amp;amp;utm_source=link&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Protect the Coral Reefs&lt;/a&gt; by Pranav Thandassery
&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-and-communication-technology&#34;&gt;Information and Communication Technology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://elproschoolspune-my.sharepoint.com/:p:/g/personal/anay_bilwalkar_elproschools_edu_in/EeJNi_0l7YNBqXM8n-LHsEYB1uG5aWzjRf6XLJ3jXAJvqw?e=VkdEiJ&amp;amp;nav=eyJzSWQiOjI3NSwiY0lkIjo4MjQzODgwNzh9&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/p/homework-archive/earthgame.png&#34;
	width=&#34;1268&#34;
	height=&#34;263&#34;
	srcset=&#34;/p/homework-archive/earthgame_hu548da14829d2b3b69eaa3678e3b04705_86823_480x0_resize_box_3.png 480w, /p/homework-archive/earthgame_hu548da14829d2b3b69eaa3678e3b04705_86823_1024x0_resize_box_3.png 1024w&#34;
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Earth Games&#34;
	
	
		class=&#34;gallery-image&#34; 
		data-flex-grow=&#34;482&#34;
		data-flex-basis=&#34;1157px&#34;
	
&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-own-projects-wip&#34;&gt;My own projects (w.i.p):&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is incomplete cuz i couldnt finish this whole site in a day&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Report</title>
        <link>/p/report/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 21:36:20 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/report/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="/clip_image004.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Report" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global Perspectives
&lt;strong&gt;THE BED CRISIS&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;sup&gt;&lt;sub&gt;And possible solutions.&lt;/sub&gt; &lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hospitals around the world were unable to handle the demand brought on by Covid-19 (also known as the Coronavirus), which resulted in what many refer to as the &amp;ldquo;Bed Crisis,&amp;rdquo; when patients&amp;rsquo; need for beds skyrocketed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened-to-cause-this&#34;&gt;What happened to cause this?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During the first few years of the pandemic, little was known about Covid, leaving hospitals and clinics unable to prepare for the onslaught of patients catching Coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This happened because of the virus’s ability to spread, hospitals were caught off guard by the sheer amount of people needing immediate care. Due to this, hospitals were not able to sufficiently provide enough beds to critical patients, leading to the unavailability of ICUs and essential equipment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-impact&#34;&gt;The Impact&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sudden lack of space to house patients aggravated the severity of the virus and increased confirmed cases and deaths, significantly lengthening the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In India, the surge of patients, continued to rise around the country to never-before-seen highs, resulting in many deaths that could have easily been avoided.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whereas in Massachusetts, the percentage of covid victims that needed to be hospitalized was actually not that big, (about 5%), but due to the sheer volume of people infected by Covid, the hospital was still filled to its brim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The demand for emergency room beds was so high at UMass Memorial Medical Center, that some patients had to be cared for in hallways, with privacy barriers put up between beds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;There is no capacity for patients right now in the UMass system,&amp;rdquo; Hospital epidemiologist Dr. Richard Ellison said. &amp;ldquo;As soon as someone gets discharged, the bed is filled immediately.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Resulting in numerous and unnecessary complications to the patient&amp;rsquo;s health, putting them at risk and, in some cases, resulting in death. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;proposed-solution&#34;&gt;Proposed Solution&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The solution to the hospital bed crisis is a multi-sided one, depending entirely on various factors such as the resources available, and the will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some possible solutions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Increase hospital bed capacity: This should be a no-brainer, possibly involving expanding hospitals or building new ones entirely&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Optimize the hospital discharge process: Many patients remain in hospitals far longer than necessary, and improving the hospital discharge process would greatly benefit the system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prioritize resource allocation: During times of crisis, it is essential to prioritize resource allocation based on patients&amp;rsquo; needs, possibly meaning reallocating staff and resources from non-essential services&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;whats-already-in-effect&#34;&gt;What’s already in effect?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on the region and the cause of the crisis, various measures have been implemented to address the hospital bed crisis. These measures include building new hospitals or expanding existing ones, temporarily suspending non-urgent procedures, and using alternative care settings such as hotels or community centres. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, telehealth services have been expanded to provide remote care to patients who do not require hospitalization, and staff from non-essential services have been redeployed to deal with increased demand. Finally, hospitals have prioritised critical care to ensure that patients needing immediate care receive it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;bibliography&#34;&gt;Bibliography&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CDC - Impact of the crisis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CNN - Facts &amp;amp; Statistics&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BBC - Victims&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PUNETIMES - Victims and localized statistics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;JACOBIN - Data &amp;amp; Examples&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>dog</title>
        <link>/p/dog/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 12:29:58 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/dog/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is for an English assignment, and is extremely incomplete&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br&gt;
It was Tuesday and I had a long sports class at school. I was very tired. On the bus ride home, I was excited to see my dog Chewie. He always greeted me at the door with excitement, showing me his toys and asking for treats. Usually, we played for about ten minutes. But when I got home and opened the door, Chewie wasn&amp;rsquo;t there. I searched for him and found him under my study desk, looking tired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When Chewie saw me, he perked up a little, but still seemed tired. I gave him some water to drink, which helped a bit. Then, I took him outside to play and made him run around in a field near our home. He was very happy and energetic after that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-you-should-do-in-this-situation&#34;&gt;What you should do in this situation.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If your dog is looking a little tired, give him/her some water and food, and try playing with him/her for a while, if he/she stays tired, consider getting an appointment at a veterinarian near you. As your dog might be sick, In my case, he just needed a little love and attention.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Should Children Bring Phones to School</title>
        <link>/p/should-children-bring-phones-to-school/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 14:32:23 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/should-children-bring-phones-to-school/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://i.guim.co.uk/img/media/4c01eedc2145201d405e67fc8b7165d677cf3dd8/0_40_640_384/master/640.jpg?width=1200&height=1200&quality=85&auto=format&fit=crop&s=44b2aa45d5708e8d8081f2b75abaa733" alt="Featured image of post Should Children Bring Phones to School" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children all across the world yearn to bring their phones to school, for educational reasons, and to play music on the bus. Should children be allowed to bring phones to school?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-downsides&#34;&gt;The downsides&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phones would give leeway to a lot of academic dishonor, from cheating on exams to using a calculator in maths class. Having a phone in class would make cheating a lot easier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It would also lead to a lot of liability for the school, as storing a complex electronic device could lead to possible damage to the device, as well as to technological vulnerabilities in the school&amp;rsquo;s ecosystem, making it easier to &amp;ldquo;hack&amp;rdquo; into computers and potentially steal future exam papers/tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;in-conclusion&#34;&gt;In conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t think children should be allowed to bring phones to school, as it would put a lot of responsibility on the child, and liability on the school.
However, grades above 10th should be allowed to bring electronic devices as the class teacher sees fit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Why Swimming Is Good for You</title>
        <link>/p/why-swimming-is-good-for-you/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:25:53 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/why-swimming-is-good-for-you/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://images.pexels.com/photos/711187/pexels-photo-711187.jpeg?auto=compress&cs=tinysrgb&w=1260&h=750&dpr=1" alt="Featured image of post Why Swimming Is Good for You" /&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-swimming-is-good-for-you&#34;&gt;Why swimming is good for you&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have you ever wondered why so many people choose swimming as their go-to form of exercise?
Well, Swimming has numerous benefits for your body, ranging from cardiovascular fitness to stretching muscles you&amp;rsquo;ve never used before as you propel yourself through the water
&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.pexels.com/photos/711187/pexels-photo-711187.jpeg?auto=compress&amp;amp;cs=tinysrgb&amp;amp;w=1260&amp;amp;h=750&amp;amp;dpr=1&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Person Swimming&#34;
	
	
&gt;
You&amp;rsquo;ll find swimming to be an excellent way to improve your fitness, as it&amp;rsquo;s a high-gain activity that exercises your whole body, from your arms and legs to your core, and unlike most other forms of exercise, swimming can keep you fit without putting much strain on your joints!
Furthermore, according to surveys, most swimmers feel that their mood is greatly improved after swimming. 
It&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to have fun and cool off, from a pool party with friends on a hot day, to a game of friendly water polo.
If you start incorporating swimming into your routine, you&amp;rsquo;ll see and feel the benefits for yourself, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be more confident, happier, and healthier.
So, make a splash in your life and start swimming today!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Why Writing Is Good for Children</title>
        <link>/p/why-writing-is-good-for-children/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 18:50:36 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/why-writing-is-good-for-children/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://images.indianexpress.com/2021/02/pixabay_child-writing_1200.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Why Writing Is Good for Children" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://images.indianexpress.com/2021/02/pixabay_child-writing_1200.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Child Writing&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-writing-is-important-for-children&#34;&gt;Why writing is important for children&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing can mean different things to different people.
Some people find it makes them at peace.
Other people find it makes them money.
Ask a child and all you&amp;rsquo;ll hear are complaints and groans.
Yet there is no denying, that writing is an essential part of all our lives, from writing emails to your teacher to posting on a forum;
writing is important for us all - children and adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing is an important part of any child&amp;rsquo;s education. Across the world, children are required to write essays as an integral part of their curriculum. As a student myself, I hate writing, but I can see the wisdom in it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing is an essential skill for children, as it further enables their ability to express themselves, and develop their creativity and it improves their handwriting too!
Writing is a lifelong skill that is important for personal and professional success, it is important to start early and nurture it throughout a child&amp;rsquo;s life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Twitters Downfall</title>
        <link>/p/twitters-downfall/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 15:49:43 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/twitters-downfall/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fbucketeer-e05bbc84-baa3-437e-9518-adb32be77984.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F26776053-8035-478b-a4f1-31a43e6aefe4_1024x1024.png" alt="Featured image of post Twitters Downfall" /&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;prologue&#34;&gt;Prologue&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unless you&amp;rsquo;re living under a rock, you would know that Elon Musk bought Twitter. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;for-all-the-people-living-in-a-cave&#34;&gt;For all the people living in a cave&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter is the world&amp;rsquo;s largest micro-blogging app, rivaled only by Koo, it also happens to be the worst place to share your opinion, Rivaled only by a school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Originally, Twitter was meant to be a place where you could share anything you want - from your daily life to your opinion on the news -
without having to worry about being suppressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;however&#34;&gt;However&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this point, It&amp;rsquo;s turned into a cesspool of controversies and cancel culture.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/hW1p33J.png&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;You were the chosen one!&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter is slowly crumbling into the abyss of dead apps, almost fully thanks to a certain multi-billionaire whose name rhymes with &amp;ldquo;nylon tusk&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Diary of a Wimpy Kid Diper Överlode Book Review</title>
        <link>/p/diary-of-a-wimpy-kid-diper-%C3%B6verlode-book-review/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 19:50:28 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/diary-of-a-wimpy-kid-diper-%C3%B6verlode-book-review/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://i.pinimg.com/originals/d4/ba/e1/d4bae1e6e5a7b47827e477093b15525c.jpg#center" alt="Featured image of post Diary of a Wimpy Kid Diper Överlode Book Review" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://rukminim1.flixcart.com/image/416/416/xif0q/regionalbooks/g/n/p/diary-of-a-wimpy-kid-diper-overload-by-jeff-kinney-english-original-imagjtgm98btksgz.jpeg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Image&#34;
	
	
&gt;
Im sure all of you can guess by the title, that there&amp;rsquo;s alot of potty humor in this. I mean, Loded Diper has been an iconic name for as long as I can remember
Diper Överlode was an unexpected but welcome addition to the &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.amazon.in/s?k=diary&amp;#43;of&amp;#43;a&amp;#43;wimpy&amp;#43;kid&amp;#43;book&amp;#43;sets&amp;amp;adgrpid=62819624395&amp;amp;ext_vrnc=hi&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQiA1ZGcBhCoARIsAGQ0kkqv4FexzJHIaPKxvzc3Phkz8psnuPHxgZ_HVB9dOJgj1AG_VYMKJUcaApG4EALw_wcB&amp;amp;hvadid=590652605956&amp;amp;hvdev=c&amp;amp;hvlocphy=9062088&amp;amp;hvnetw=g&amp;amp;hvqmt=b&amp;amp;hvrand=16181495951405344527&amp;amp;hvtargid=kwd-300731490699&amp;amp;hydadcr=24511_2265429&amp;amp;tag=googinhydr1-21&amp;amp;ref=pd_sl_7m4y3ru8y6_b&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;Diary of a Wimpy Kid&lt;/a&gt; series, although not containing much, it was an enjoyable read for me and all my classmates.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;spoiler-alert&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spoiler alert!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h6 id=&#34;but-you-knew-that&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;(but you knew that)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;educational-value&#34;&gt;Educational Value&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;b-&#34;&gt;B-&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain much, but teaches readers the value of music, and how much artists strive for the spotlight, however small that spotlight is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;addition-to-story&#34;&gt;Addition to Story&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;b&#34;&gt;B+&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reveals &lt;strong&gt;spoiler alert&lt;/strong&gt; Loded Dipers origin story and Rodricks inspiration, &lt;em&gt;Thankfully&lt;/em&gt; doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain Manny (phew).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-its-about&#34;&gt;What it&amp;rsquo;s about&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In DIARY OF A WIMPY KID: DIPER OVERLODE, Greg doesn&amp;rsquo;t want all the hassle of being famous and losing his privacy. He&amp;rsquo;d rather have famous friends &amp;ndash; or even better, famous family so he always gets expensive gifts for the holidays. He thinks his best bet in that regard is his brother Rodrick, who plays drums in the metal band Loded Diper. Rodrick really wants fame, too, and does everything he can to get the band noticed. Well, everything he can on a budget, that is. Instead of professional band photos, his mom plays photographer in their backyard with her cell phone. Instead of a sweet ride for their band equipment, they acquire an old ice cream truck. When they finally get one track recorded in a studio &amp;ndash; after a scary incident with a swallowed guitar pick &amp;ndash; no one will play the song. When they finally get a gig at a local dive, Rodrick forgets his drumsticks. That puts Greg, their roadie, on the spot to steal a pair in a hurry from a very unlikely, extra creepy place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;— &lt;cite&gt;commonsensemedia.org&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;overall-recommend-library-metre&#34;&gt;Overall recommend (library-metre)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;100% recommend it to a library that allows children to enter and read. This book has some great values (like saying no to vandalising) and some really good english.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Extreme Sports</title>
        <link>/p/extreme-sports/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/extreme-sports/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://www.adventureinyou.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/08/what-not-to-do-bungee_5_LEAD.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Extreme Sports" /&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;are-extreme-sports-dangerous-and-do-they-deserve-to-be-prohibited&#34;&gt;Are Extreme sports dangerous? And do they deserve to be prohibited?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-are-extreme-sports&#34;&gt;What are extreme sports?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extreme sports, also commonly referred to as action sports, are competitive sports that are characterized by high risk. Skateboarding, snowboarding, freestyle skiing, and mountain biking are the sports that are most frequently included in this category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extreme sports are typically performed outside the boundaries of traditional mainstream sports and are renowned for their heart-pounding thrills. Motorcycle and snowmobile racing and acrobatic competitions are frequently categorized as &amp;ldquo;extreme,&amp;rdquo; and the term can be interpreted to include risky activities like skydiving and rock climbing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-does-one-tell-the-difference&#34;&gt;How does one tell the difference?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ask yourself the question, is Soccer an extreme sport?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No right?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yet, More than 775,000 children annually get hospitalized while playing Soccer.
And there have been more than 10 deaths ON TV.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider base jumping: what would happen if the wind suddenly changed direction while you were speeding through a canyon?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-do-people-pursue-extreme-sports&#34;&gt;Why do people pursue extreme sports?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you love the swoop in your stomach as you plummet down a swing, wind gushing through your ears, pulling back your hair, Then extreme sports are for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thrill of doing something dangerous can only be achieved &lt;strong&gt;by&lt;/strong&gt; doing something dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Often people achieve great feats only by assuming a tremendous risk for themselves, take, for example, the act of summating a mountain like Everest, would you do it if it was easy?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many extreme sports allow one to feel the freedom to challenge themselves, physically and psychologically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;do-they-deserve-to-be-banned&#34;&gt;Do they deserve to be banned?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;in-conclusion&#34;&gt;In Conclusion&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though engaging in extreme sports could be very dangerous, I still believe they should be pursued with well-established safety guidelines and with caution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People who explore extreme sports, do so with the knowledge of the associated dangers &lt;strong&gt;and&lt;/strong&gt; with the intent of seeking a thrill. Banning extreme sports would be like banning people from summiting Mount Everest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How would &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; feel if you were banned from sitting on swings simply because of an inherent danger of falling off and hurting yourself?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>What&#39;s It Like Owning a Dog</title>
        <link>/p/whats-it-like-owning-a-dog/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 19:44:55 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/whats-it-like-owning-a-dog/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;prologue&#34;&gt;Prologue&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;rsquo;m sure you all have debated about having a dog, whether it be as a companion, guard-dog, or a emotional support pet (in my case, yes). But then you realise how much of a pain in the backside it can be, all the way from potty training, to even simple manners&amp;hellip; In that case, this blog is for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-upsides&#34;&gt;The upsides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all know how cute dogs are, and even a street dog can smile its way out of a jam. So, here are some advantages to owning one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A dog makes &lt;strong&gt;you&lt;/strong&gt; more awesome - The commitment to taking care of a - adorable, but nonetheless - mooch, that couldn&amp;rsquo;t last a day without you. It makes you more empathic and all-round improves your personaly - Plus dogs are a great conversation starter - .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dogs rewire the way you think - I know I sound like a broken recorder right now, but as I said before, committing to a dog will change the way you think, and bad moods will become moderate, and good moods will become great moods!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owning a dog improves your physical and mental health - Your dog would require constant exercise, and so would you! Dog owners carry a responsibility to exercise/play alongside their dogs. Like whenever I take my dog down, I make sure he gets alot of exercise before returning - On the days I want to sleep, that is!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do I need to say more?
&lt;img src=&#34;/dog_%281%29.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;image&#34;
	
	
&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;/dog_%282%29.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;image&#34;
	
	
&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;/dog_%283%29.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;image&#34;
	
	
&gt; &lt;img src=&#34;/dog_%284%29.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;image&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Why I Made This Blog</title>
        <link>/p/why-i-made-this-blog/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2022 18:20:26 +0530</pubDate>
        
        <guid>/p/why-i-made-this-blog/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s rewarding to be able to move readers with your writing. That’s why I decided to create a blog. &lt;img src=&#34;/person_Writing.jpg&#34;
	
	
	
	loading=&#34;lazy&#34;
	
		alt=&#34;Person writing&#34;
	
	
&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-inspire-my-audience1&#34;&gt;To Inspire My audience&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing a blog allows one to express ones feelings and air out ones judgements about life, It could also affect the readers life by allowing them to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve their quality of life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase their day&amp;rsquo;s output.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make something lovely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lend a hand to others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of this is possible thanks to the power of a blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-improve-my-writing-ability&#34;&gt;To improve my writing ability&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting a blog had made a significant impact on my writing skills, it allowed me to express myself better, Starting out was a little strange and awkward at first. However, after I found something to write about, I found that writing became easier as I got into the swing of things. I was able to speak more effectively, and create a style that is entirely my own (mostly). I gained a solid understanding of how hard it was to write a blog. It challenged my creativity and encouraged me to write on more topics. Win-Win!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;to-confront-your-fears&#34;&gt;To confront your fears&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blogging gave me a platform to shout from – a way to confront my fear of being noticed, It allowed me to face my fear of being seen. And as a result, I came to the realization that others exist who are just like me. There are numerous additional strategies for using blogging to face your fears. It can be used to get over impostor syndrome and inferiority complexes. Writing about a subject that makes you uncomfortable can be cathartic and aid in the release of those feelings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;it-could-even-be-a-journal&#34;&gt;It could even be a journal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, a lot of individuals use blogging as a tool to support them in their battles with mental health. This demonstrates that starting a blog doesn&amp;rsquo;t always have to be a carefully thought-out project. It may simply be a place for you to gather your thoughts at times. Let us return to the beginnings of blogging. A blog was a place where you could write about your daily life. I think I have an old dear-diary style book dedicated to that somewhere. However, just because it has fallen out of favor in recent years does not preclude you from starting a blog for that reason. Blogging about your life is an excellent way to reflect. To some extent, past joys and mistakes can be learned from. Having a place to keep your memories can help you see how far you&amp;rsquo;ve come and how much you&amp;rsquo;ve learned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Starting a blog has advantages and disadvantages, and there is no one-size-fits-all solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consider both sides of the argument and weigh them against your own personality, lifestyle, and ambitions when deciding whether or not to start a blog. Examine your options and be honest about what you truly want from the experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ll be the one doing the work, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be the one reaping the benefits in the end. Remember: &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;Writing is a marathon. Not a sprint.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; - Robert McKee&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heavily Inspired from &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://bloggingwizard.com/reasons-to-start-a-blog/&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;this blog.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
